Star.
Command.
-Command.
-Star.
-Meeting with Star Command.
Meeting with Star Command, Meeting with the...
Star Command, Meeting with Star Command.
Meeting with Star Command.
List!
That way you won't lose me, Jessy.
Friends forever, Cowgirl.
Well said, cowgirl.
But don't be alarmed.
I'm going to watch you from here.
Do you know?
I'm still watching you!
Leave...
And I'll be back!
I can still see you!
Oh no!
Leave!
And I'm going to love you...
All the time, even when you're furious, or sad,
or I accidentally left you out.
I will love you forever.
Oh really?
Are you not lying?
Forever and ever?
Yes. Everything forever.
Do you, Forky, take
Karen Beverly to be your beloved wife?
I accept!
And you, Karen Beverly?
I now pronounce you husband and wife!
Kiss, kiss!
Who poisoned the maid of honor?
Because?!
Attention!
Get out of the way!
I know CPR!
One two three!
Now, the kiss of life!
But we didn't solve my murder!
Don't stay where you are, Rex!
Dolly, what's going on?!
Oh, I'm not sure!
At first I was annoyed that Bonnie drew me
These glasses, but honestly, now I look
much better with them.
¡Dolly, atenta!
Oops, sorry!
They're the Jordan twins!
They're back!
Are you still afraid to talk to them?
Not this time!
¡Arre, arre!
And Bonnie?
You can do it!
Hello!
Oh, Jessie, the wedding got me thinking...
¡Shh!
Something is wrong!
Tell us, is the wedding over yet?
Who killed the lady this time?
Mother?
Dad?
Yes, baby.
Why does nobody want to be my friend?
Oh, Bonnie, come!
¡Boss!
You are my sheriff!
I'll be right back!
They?
Of course!
I'm going to have the twins play with
Bonnie.
Somehow!
Come, target practice!
They're just sitting there, doing nothing.
They are not playing with any toys.
That?
Didn't you hear?
No, I'm not aware of it.
Didn't he find out?
Didn't he really find out?
That?
What didn't I know?
The toy era is over.
What do you mean it ended?
Since when did this happen?
It's been going on for years!
Where were you?
I was playing across the street.
Playing?
Oh!
Does your little girl still play?
I've already forgotten what it looks like.
Describe it to me.
Is everyone okay?
What happened to them?
Technology!
Gadgets!
Everywhere!
Telephones!
Wallpaper!
Computers!
Cameras!
The screens!
They guessed us!
And the tapping!
Writing!
Oh!
They've already forgotten about us!
Take my advice.
Find a drawer and hide.
When technology arrives, wherever you are, you'll stay.
It's most likely a fad.
Just like those record players or the hoops of
hula.
You don't understand.
The toy era is over!
Term!
Oh!
Don't you believe us?
Come and see it for yourself.
Look at those children.
Everyone with devices.
Except for Bonnie.
No wonder he can't make friends, he shot at
white.
She's the only one who still plays with toys.
Quiet.
We are safe.
Are we sure about this?
No, but maybe this will help.
Ok.
First Flight?
Oh!
Thank you!
Thanks, Mom!
Thanks, Dad!
Well, you're already eight and we think you're...
list.
Hello, I'm Lilipad.
Welcome to the pond.
You can use it today to learn how it works, but
From tomorrow there will be a different network
for use.
I can try.
Keep jumping.
Good morning.
No more screens.
Put Lilipad away and go downstairs for breakfast.
Ok.
I'm going upstairs to talk to that woman.
Lilipad and explain to her how things are done
here.
Stay calm, Jessie.
What are you talking about?
Carman is my middle name.
It's not going to work.
¡Oh!
Sorry, I didn't mean to scare you.
It's my sleep mode.
¿No?
Uh, forget it.
I'm going to plug into my charger to refresh.
the battery.
We need to talk about the device.
Please, call me Lily.
Look, Lily.
The toys and I worked all summer
so that Boris could become friends with the
Jordan twins from the house across the street, but
Now you're ruined.
Everything about your wedding?
You're not even listening to me.
Oh!
No, I was listening.
I'm always listening, you see?
Look, Lily.
The toys and I worked all summer
so that Boris could become friends with the
Jordan twins.
Now in English.
Bonnie and the boys have been working all
summer to try and get Bonnie to make
friends with the Jordan.
Now as rap.
All summer long we toys worked so that
Bonnie and...
Our first dance!
¡Oh!
I have ethical problems.
You obviously don't understand.
Our little girl needs to learn how to be friends.
And you're not helping him with your screen.
If Bonnie needs friends, consider what's been done.
List.
That?
I don't know, I don't know what happened.
Oh!
It was easy.
Send a friend request to the girls
from her dance class.
But the thing is...
They are not here.
¡Oh!
Of course they are.
Plot.
Chelsea, Cara and even Heidi.
They're all there.
The parents created a group chat in the
pond.
You'll see, in the pond, while Bonnie is having fun
and learn with my games, socialize with others
children.
That's why their parents bought me.
To make connections.
So!
She made a friend.
I want one.
That little pad gave Bonnie a friend
in a few...
15 seconds.
I counted them.
That?
¡No!
Don't touch.
She's not just a friend, she's a real friend.
I would be present.
That's my point.
Jessica.
Oh, no!
She said the name with drops of blood.
What a scandal!
With my help, Bonnie is slowly but surely getting there
to achieve their development goals.
He just wants what's best for her.
I think it's better than a green calculator,
which is best for Bonnie.
You think?
Yes, I believe so.
I have three children of experience.
Bonnie, but before that there was Andy.
And long before that there was Emily.
That just shows you're old.
Oh!
Wow!
How old-fashioned!
Okay, let's fight for it.
Oh!
Fight with yourself!
What are you doing, you little pigs?
I'm going to kiss you from the bed!
Fight if you dare, you scoundrel!
Pass me by!
Who is better for Bonnie?
Who said you could lift me up?
¡Bonnie!
I'm coming!
That?
Is something wrong?
The guy from the dance class invited me
to a sleepover.
I can go!
Well, if that's what you want, on the condition that
Let her talk to her parents, then I'll leave you alone.
and.
Yeah!
Okay, let's have breakfast.
I want to stay behind the dresser.
I can be there for a few years.
Ah, extinction!
No, not again!
Relax!
This is not the end yet.
Bonnie still loves us.
Of course!
Whatever you say, commissioner.
It's just a phase!
Hola, Capumaki.
Change?
¡Oh, Duke!
How are you, Red?
How long?
Hello.
Is Woody there?
I won't be long!
Hey, cowboy!
For your motorcycle!
He's on a rescue mission!
¡¿Tardilla mala?!
¡No!
Yeah!
Little!
Evil!
¡No!
Okay, Mr. Loquaz!
Listen!
¡Doctor!
¡Ok, doctor Loquaz!
On the count of three you'll detach yourself from
that ribbon to fall into my arms!
So that?
The toys lost!
The screens won!
And now it's late!
It's going to eat you!
Are you ready?
Just one message!
Come!
And bring me the videos I got stuck on
the tree!
We're doomed!
¡Ok!
A!
Of the!
Oh, I'm laughing!
It's over now.
Don't cry.
I'm not worth it.
Hello!
Jessie!
¡Woody!
Hello!
What have you done to yourself?
I hate you, technology!
We are useless insects!
¡Woody!
Is it really that bad for toys now?
They say?
Always the machines!
Yes, yes.
It's serious.
More toys are being abandoned every day.
Because?
Is everything alright there?
Not so much.
Technology has also invaded us.
Oh, no!
Yes, it's called Lilypuff.
It looks like a frog, but it's a leech that
It sucks all of Bonnie's attention.
It makes you look at your screen all day.
There has to be a way to stop her!
I'm not sure, Jessie.
We're good for playing, but technology is good for
all.
¡Wow!
Emily, my first daughter.
Do you remember her?
Did I ever tell you that he gave me the
final?
Of course I remember!
It's as if everything is repeating itself.
One day we were playing and the next it all started
to change.
I know!
Emily changed, and suddenly, just like that.
My time with her is over.
Now I'm losing Bonnie to this device.
Is it because of me?
Maybe it's because I'm not a
good toy.
Jessie, you're a great toy!
I don't know, Woody.
Jessie!
Jessie?
No, commissioner.
My Jessie honors me with this promotion, but
What he would like to promote is his great, silly voice.
And she arranged for Bonnie to be invited to
a slumber party in seconds.
Jessie, you know Bonnie better than anyone.
What does your instinct tell you?
That it's too easy.
Bonnie doesn't connect with just anyone.
Exact.
You need to get to know these girls well.
He is not like other children.
Bonnie plays differently.
Has...
to really play.
Jessie.
You're right, Woody.
We are good for playing.
And playing is like finding a friend.
Ok.
The toy era is over.
But I'm not going to leave without having done it.
something good.
I'm going to that sleepover and looking for
a true friend for Bonnie.
Are you OK?
¿Boss?
Jessie?
Boss, what are you doing here?
What are you doing here?
I thought you needed support.
No, I don't need support.
Something like that.
And what happened?
Why do we whisper?
He finally fell asleep.
Is something wrong?
I'm not sure, but you heard Jessie.
He needs something like that.
Machines!
Jessie?
Yes, what do you want?
Nothing, the truth was it wasn't important.
If you need anything, I'm here for you.
At your service.
OK thanks.
Come on, target practice.
You're going to have to help me.
Stars, there's a lot of fog.
We need to look for higher ground.
No, this one.
I'm not going to clean it.
Why are we standing still?
Fascinating.
We have to evade.
Humans?
Yes.
You're going to
Be well, my love.
Go put your shoes on, we're leaving now.
What are you doing?
Let's meet these friends in person to
Let's see if any of them are good for Bonnie.
Okay, pause.
It would be a disaster if Bonnie brought toys to
a sleepover.
I accept, I accept.
Something like that.
I accept.
Whatever you want to say.
Don't let that device take over.
You're welcome while we're gone.
Whatever you say, police station.
We're leaving now.
No, Jessie, get out of the suitcase.
I'm only interested in doing what's best for Bonnie.
What a coincidence, that's exactly what I'm saying.
doing so as well.
What happened, Jessie?
Oh, thank you!
You put Jessie in and she already hit the target.
I did it?
Well, you're welcome.
And we're almost there.
Oh, how nerve-wracking!
Have Kara and Heidi arrived yet?
Oh, there they are, Bob!
I already saw them!
Park!
Okay, okay, I've seen them.
¡Ey, Bonnie!
Your suitcase!
Hello, Jessie.
Oh, hi, Bonnie.
Hey, do you remember Bonnie?
Hello.
And she is Jessie.
I'm not afraid of anything, cowgirl.
Do you still use toys?
No, I'm going for a reason.
Leave your things.
Oh, keep them safe!
But didn't you want your toys?
No, keep them!
Look, he's bringing my cleaning too!
Oh, no.
Someone forgot their toys.
What did you say?
I said someone forgot their toys!
Let's see...
Oh, her owner's name is Emily.
And it has an address.
It's not very far from here.
Let's leave them alone!
Turn right onto Branch Road.
You have arrived at your destination.
I'm going to leave them in the mailbox.
What did you say?
Are you going to leave me?
Yeah!
No, no, no!
We can't stay here!
We have to go back to Bonnie!
Come on, let's go to the target!
Yeah!
I can speak your language and set this up...
It's for the other side!
To the other side!
Stop, please!
Target shooting!
Are you OK?
Come, help me.
Albert, what's wrong?
Are you OK?
Did something frighten you?
Come here, little one.
Get in.
That.
And where did you come from?
It's perfect.
¡No!
Target shooting!
And how is this going to attract attention?
From Bonnie, according to you?
Well, when they get back from the sleepover...
Careful!
Bonnie is going in, she'll see Forky and
Karen Beverly will remember the wedding.
But we are talking about Bonnie, right?
And not Jessie's.
Yeah.
Of course, from Bonnie!
Alone...
¿Bonnie?
What are they doing?
What are they talking about?
Today he will propose to Jessie.
Marriage?
No, no, no.
Wait, wait, hold on a moment.
I never said that.
Didn't you say he won't either?
Who, you?
One question.
Is Woody going to officiate the wedding ceremony?
I haven't thought that far ahead, Forky.
Ok.
And what's Woody doing at the window?
Hello friends.
It's nice to see them.
There is nobody on stage.
It's yours, my friend.
What a treat!
Handsome cowboy.
Why are you wearing a dress, Woody?
This is a poncho, Forky.
It's a new look.
Well, Bo likes it.
It's great to be back.
That?
What a lovely poncho.
Someone needs a brown marker.
Wow, it looks like Bonnie redecorated the room.
It's, it's somewhat careless.
How beautiful.
Oh, and Sammy grew a lot.
Is Sammy number two?
No.
Yeah.
I'll explain.
We had a number one Sammy and then he died.
Poor wise man.
High!
Who's there?
No, no, stop.
No, sorry.
My name is Woody and I come in peace.
I used to live here.
You win.
Years have passed, Cowboy.
Where have you been?
Ah, busy.
I ran here when Jesse called for backup.
Luckily we were close by.
Are you a cat?
Yeah.
But I am your sheriff.
That was weird.
Well, there must be a slight misunderstanding.
Well, don't take offense, Woody.
No, no, I know, I know.
But he appointed me his sheriff, literally.
Ah, that's it, that's it.
Woody, over here, take a look.
Estrella named me.
No star.
Yes, I understand now.
With a star.
No star.
What is that thing?
What thing?
Hey, wait.
I only came to help the sheriff.
Let me know when you're finished helping.
Thanks, Bo.
Ready, ladies?
Girls' party.
Yeah.
On you.
By the way, where's Jesse?
Sleepover mission.
Bullseye helps Bonnie to be
friends.
And they defend her from the wicked Ladybug.
I'm Dolly, by the way.
With glasses.
Didn't you have them before?
That?
¡No!
There's no problem here.
I bet Jessie is resting in a soft
pillow and is making a huge difference for
Bonnie.
You're just standing there watching.
I know!
Can you help me get out of here?
Come here!
Come, come!
Almond!
Yes, yes!
Can come!
Come on!
Come here!
Cute pig!
I'm a fish!
How nice!
I think you're going to help me.
Ham?
How the...? Oh no!
Okay.
Wow!
Is that your name, Jamoncín?
Take me home with you!
With my grandfather's shovels!
It's working!
Hey!
No, no, no, no, no!
Yeah!
Yes, what a good little pig!
You're good, you are!
¡No!
No, no, no!
Bad pig!
That's not the house!
Oh, no!
No, Jamoncín!
You're not here!
¡No!
See?
False alarm, folks!
What a shame!
Sorry for the Kombat Card mugs.
Welcome, please sit down.
¡Oh!
No, I have to go now.
No no!
Sit down!
Kombat Card insists!
¡Oh, ok!
No, no, no, no, no!
Sorry, sorry!
Any chair but that one!
Who sits there?
¡Blaze!
Are they talking about the girl in the stable?
Is she your daughter?
Isn't it adorable!
He loves Kun's parties!
And tell us all their secrets.
That's right, pizza with sunglasses.
For Blaze and his return!
¡Mmm, rico!
How long ago did Blaze throw a party?
do you have here?
When he arrived, things changed a lot.
He?
Smarty Pants was their first gadget.
She is sitting on it.
That?
Sugary gummies!
Hello how are you?
Choose one.
Number one.
Or number two.
Silence!
What did I deserve to do?
Let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see!
This!
¡No!
This is not the bathroom.
How long was I switched off?
Yeah I know!
Delete it!
Oh!
¡No!
Delete it!
Where did this... come from
Grandmother!
Oh, a cat knows what's wrong!
Low battery!
This is the bathroom.
¡Eggman!
You're a shelf gadget!
Finally, I have to stick it out here to fit in!
I don't have time for this!
I went up and centered the house with my
horse!
And we have to go back to our little girl!
Let's see, let's see, let's see!
Are you going into the house?
Take me with you, finally!
Don't even joke about it!
I'll help you push!
I'm the best pusher!
It's gone, it's gone!
It brought a lot of rain!
Stay here and wait with your friends!
Oh, and spend another second with the corporal!
Without pants?
¡No!
I'm coming with you, cowgirl!
Don't even think about it!
Those in your class are just trouble!
My class?
Take it away, take it away!
Only serve your black pudding!
I am not a chair!
I'm a bathroom trainer!
Show respect!
Listen, little doll.
These weeping ones are for outdoor use.
I'm the only one who has lived inside...
Looking for your hair, Clevity Club?
Exactly where Blaze put it, okay?
You need me!
You need me, you need me, you need me so much!
It was!
Oh, my eyes!
Can someone turn down the lights?
Can you walk without shaking me so fast?
Close down before they change their minds!
Understood.
High!
Only your backpack will do!
I'm sure it's this way.
Hurt!
Here's the line, we follow it, and here
There's the camp.
Ah, I understand now.
Yes, it's this way.
Don't leave me, don't leave me!
Wow!
Luis, go away!
Hey, Mommy!
Look at this!
¡Blaze!
I'm going out!
I'll be back in an hour!
Wait!
I forgot my keys!
Hey, I don't feel well at all.
I think I'm going to restart.
¡Blaze!
Be quiet!
Where?
I'm back.
I went back home.
This is where it all began.
Yeah.
It's different.
¡Smarty, no!
I have to find Tilo the White.
Wake up!
I need more energy.
Okay, where are the batteries?
Where can I find the batteries?
Bottom drawer, next to the stamps.
Hello!
How are you?
Choose it!
Number one!
Wow!
I feel so good!
Look at me!
¡No!
We're not going to do this now!
I said no!
Don't turn around!
Be quiet!
¡Snappy!
¡Atlas!
Are they still here?!
Oh!
¡Shock!
We need to turn them on!
¡No!
I don't want to!
We don't need any more gadgets!
What?
But how?
Are you going to leave them in the dark forever?
Do you know what it feels like?
Alright!
But we won't be long.
Oh, yes!
Number one!
¡Atlas!
¡Snappy!
It's you?
Is that really you?
I can't believe it!
You look like new!
Type A!
It's back!
Mom brought us inside when Blaze had that tantrum
And we never saw you again!
Okay, tell me.
What did you ask me for?
The truth is that we've also been in storage for a while.
Oh!
But look!
You can watch it in first and second grade!
Yeah!
Please!
¡Mirenla!
It grew so much!
Isn't that right?
It's adorable!
In other words, that year he let his hair grow out.
From what moment?
Where were they?
Disneyland!
¡Dame zoom!
There I am!
Wow!
It was the rocks!
Yeah!
Everything was beautiful!
And, oh, that's all I have.
There was a rainbow wheel spinning.
Then, darkness.
My memory card passed in front of me
eyes.
Wow!
¡Ok!
It's great that they have energy again!
But we're wasting time I don't have!
We are grateful, Miss Baquerita!
Do you want to tell them something?
She is the annoying Jessie the Baker.
She says she's the police commissioner.
Tell him yes.
Does Blaze have his horse White Bull?
Yes, White Bull!
And our little girl Bonnie is waiting for us in
home.
He needs us!
Where are you, Marty?
Relax.
I said I would tell you and I will.
say.
Let the drums come.
He's probably in his room.
Probably in his room?
I guessed it!
But you didn't, Rancia.
Stale?
Yes, like a stuck, smelly gas.
I tell them number 1.5. You know what?
I don't have to put up with it.
Wait!
I have an idea that might help you
to go back to Bonnie.
Which?
Well, it's a bit technical, but if the
The three of us got enameled...
No no.
No incomprehensible technological plans.
No offense, but I can find a way back
alone.
Yes, I was offended!
He's been silenced, Dave.
Your microphone.
Okay, now we're talking.
I'll repeat it, Dave.
You've gone silent again!
Oh, saltine crackers!
What are you doing?
Don't go up!
You're not the only one who misses their
little girl!
¡Ok!
Give yourself a hand!
Careful!
You're not going to disconnect me!
¡Blaze!
¡Vine!
Hi, Mom!
Back, back, back!
Mother!
Just a second!
Is she our biggest Blaze?
How much has it changed?
In such a short time!
Mother!
Did she arrive?
No love!
Why don't you send him a message?
Wow, she's huge!
She...
He did his business without me.
¡Oh!
Look how cute!
Everything is clean!
I know when it's been sorted!
I can see the floor!
I can see myself on the floor!
Plus, it smells like vanilla!
It has a touch of sugar!
I tell you, I'm not surprised!
Oh, your little spot!
Yeah, seriously.
How much did we miss?
They missed everything.
Her Blaze is no longer the little girl with
the one they were playing.
And how do you know that?
I've already experienced all of this.
I spent years and years under the bed watching
to my first daughter growing up without me.
Is this our address?
How old is Blaze now?
Nine, ten?
It's a teenager's room.
He's nine and a half, just so you know.
It's because the devices make them grow so much
fast.
¡Oh!
I have to go back.
Where...
White son!
There you are!
Yes, your friends are very nice.
But we have to go now.
Let's see, let's see, let's see, let's see.
Are you saying this was your room?
Yeah.
Oh really?
Are you implying that I'm lying?
No, uh…
Yes, yes, you're lying.
There is a stain on the ceiling.
It looks like an angry eye closing its eyes.
The window has a crack that looks like a spider's.
in the upper corner of the door.
And on the swing on that hill, Emil
and I used to play every summer afternoon.
Let's go, target practice!
Oh, you're welcome!
Because?
Aren't you helping?
That?
What are you waiting for?
¡Quilo!
Useless!
That?
Oh no, he said it.
Rude!
Oh, no!
The little room!
What a great ham!
With everything, little ham!
Who's coming?
¡Sally viene!
Yes, yes.
It's coming.
He's coming to my house now.
Mother!
Sally is writing to me!
I'm sure I already...
Are you my friend?
Right, little ham?
Always.
By the way, your hair looks amazing.
Because?
Thank you, little ham.
She's perfect!
We have to get Blaze to meet Bonnie!
¿Bonnie?
You bring them!
We arrived.
Hey, baby.
How was the sleepover?
I don't want to talk about it.
Because?
What happened?
Nothing.
That doesn't sound good.
So, is Jessie there?
Calm down, they've won you over.
Your fiancée is coming.
Promised?
What were you not going to tell me?
I know, it's not exciting.
Well, it's not official anymore, Woody.
I haven't asked him yet.
I am an ordained minister, by the way.
Since when?
Since Halloween.
Bonnie dressed me up as a ghost priest.
Taxes!
Bonnie's coming!
Did you make any friends?
I think so.
Oh, how sad he looks!
Has anyone seen Jessie?
Like she's Lillipad.
Shall I make you something to eat?
Yes please.
I'm very hungry.
Jessie?
No, no, no.
It is not the correct version.
Where is Jessie?
And did he throw the ranco?
I'm helping Bonnie, I'm not sneezing.
That's what happened at the sleepover.
Excuse me, what are you?
A weird old man's toy?
That?
He thinks you're old because you're bald, Woody.
Who do you think you are?
Where is Jessie?
What happened to Bonnie?
I've never seen her so unwell.
They played hide-and-seek and forgot
look for Bonnie.
Poor Bonnie!
And you let it happen?
I didn't do it.
You did it.
The girls have been playing for over a year
in the pond, but Bonnie was delayed because
He wasted his time playing with you.
I need to get her up to speed quickly.
Summon the turtle, which is the way
faster to integrate it.
Rana, I'm asking you one last time.
Where is Jessie?
I don't care, I'm busy.
Now yes.
Speak?
Why are you talking?
I'll do it, Woody.
¡Ey!
I do it, I do it, I do it
do.
At!
Don't touch me, don't touch me.
Where is Jessie?
Ok.
I don't want them here.
Look, something bad is happening.
Goodbye, toys.
¡Oh!
Hello!
Oh, I can't!
He's not responding!
I have plastic fingers!
It's coming!
Do you really want me to take your toys?
Okay, it's your room.
If you want them, they're in the garage.
Yeah.
I now declare us stored.
Playing is fun.
Okay, what do we do now?
Take it easy, Buzz.
We're going to find her.
I promise you.
Yeah.
Woody, I know it's not a ceremony of
true, and that Bonnie is the one who decides these
things, but, well, I'd like you to be my
best man.
Buzz, it would be a true honor.
But Jessie isn't going to talk to me anymore.
because I let Lily take care of
all.
Wait a minute, damn it.
I tried not to.
No, no, Buzz, I know.
What thing?
Tomorrow morning everyone will wake up
very busy, except for Lily Parr.
And then we're going to have him tell us
Where is Jessie?
Oh, he finally fell asleep.
Ignore him.
Don't speak.
There is no one home.
I can hear them.
Smarty.
Use a distant voice.
Shut up.
Hey, camera.
Soy Snappy.
Sorry, Snappy.
You said there was a way to bring us back
con Bonnie.
Yes, tell us which one it is.
She's right, you said it.
That sounds... I don't know.
Useful?
Exactly, but we're so useful that they're useless.
I shouldn't have said they're useless.
All three have proven to be very useful
one way or another.
But what a poor excuse.
How awful that apology for that apology.
Sorry, I know I messed up.
I know I misjudged his place.
She is creative and funny.
In a way that the other children don't
They understand.
Or tell me it's not like that.
Does it continue?
Well, our little girl is just like her.
And I think they would love to meet.
It's fine if you don't want to help me, but let's help.
to our girls.
You win.
Come to blows.
Yes, good friends.
A, M, G, A.
It's with an I.
Okay, so how do we connect them?
Your daughter's device is in the
pond.
Like me, right?
Yes, and all three of them, Smart and Atlas and
We are compatible.
And I can take a picture of you.
Act like a toy.
OK.
No son fotogênicos, ¿o sí?
And Atlas can add text to the photo.
And then we released it into the pond.
Where is Bonnie?
Great, and have you sent it yet?
No, but almost.
Are you finished yet?
Hold on a little while.
What do you mean, "just a little"?
You take a very long time.
Look into my eyes, the paper is turning.
I am as fast as my system.
So lower your stress, OK?
Done, sent.
It was about time.
What now?
Now we wait.
Yes, everyone is asleep.
We have to let Bonnie wake up and see
the photo.
I have it!
We can play a game.
A game?
Yes, Blizz's favorite.
It's called Catch the Poop.
You have to press the button when the poop
appear above him.
Smarty, nothing in this world will make me play.
Everyone says that.
Kids, stop playing with your toy.
new.
Time for bed.
Until early, a little while longer?
No, time for bed.
Huh?
Mister!
While the child hugged him tightly.
all night.
That?
Dad!
Aid!
That?
What do you have?
Lili doesn't understand.
The turtle has already started playing.
Karach and the D.
Heidi play every morning.
I can't miss them.
No problem.
I already connected it.
You have to wait for it to load.
But I have to play.
I can't miss it.
Sorry, but there's nothing I can do.
It turned out great!
She was aiming!
It's phase one.
And now, phase two.
I thought I was going to start the phase...
I'm starting phase two.
I won the thumb war.
Okay, you start.
And then we're going to talk to our little friend
to the wounded.
I hate this game!
Come on, people!
Super clean!
Another one, another one, another one!
I can't feel my buttons anymore.
The last one, and that's it.
One more.
Ok, ok.
You've played enough.
Play?
They're just buttons.
That's not playing.
What's the difference?
That's when you really play.
Are you serious?
Have you ever seen Brace play with a
toy?
How long were they with her?
Three months.
Three months?
That?
Was it a lot?
It was not much.
They missed the fun part!
Are we funny?
Real fun.
Imaginary adventures.
Just take a look.
She plays.
I bet you.
Oh, really?
Prove it.
Ok, Smarty Pants.
That's what I'm going to do.
I'm arriving today, Monsi.
You're hungry, aren't you?
Mother!
Where did you find the cowgirl?
I'm not afraid of anything, cowgirl.
Let's Play!
Yeah!
One moment.
By my buttons, Brace's gonna play!
TRUE!
I'm here!
¡Milady!
¡Milady Davenport!
I represent His Royal Highness, Jamuncima I!
Your Highness!
How kind of you to invite me to your
baile real!
¡Jamunci!
It's your moment to shine!
What did you find, Jamuncí?
I didn't know I still had them around!
One moment.
Agent Clydesdale, your suitor is approaching.
We meet again, lone agent!
He speaks about health.
Restroom, did I tell you?
Agent Clydesdale, or should I say Lady Davenport?
Do you know where it is?
Are you talking about the bomb?
Yeah.
¡Calla, Snappy!
Do you have her in your sights?
Not yet.
Atlas, do you copy?
Agents!
The bomb is right where it is!
Where?
Where did you never suspect, Agent Clydesdale?
But where is the bomb?
He's waking up, Boss.
¿Boss ya vino?
That's what I'm trying to do, Woody.
What happened to me?
That?
They did something to my battery.
It's going to stay like this until you tell us.
Whatever happened to Jesse and Bullseye!
What time is it?
Oh, no!
This is not good!
The girls are already playing Touch the
Tortuga sin Bonnie!
They've shared one, two, three jokes with each other!
It's a disaster!
Your silly games don't matter.
Where are Jesse and Bullseye?
Fools?
This is serious!
¡Cappy Barabil!
He's losing the game!
Do you want me to have friends?
That's what I do!
And don't touch me with your little hands, even worse!
plastic!
I'm going to set my alarm!
I figured you wouldn't talk.
Boss, you can bring Sammy and Dos!
No no!
Take that thing away!
No, no, no, no, no!
Yeah!
Dog!
That?
Between adjustments?
This is it.
It's a gear, tighten it!
I found it.
What now?
Reduce screen time to zero.
The minimum is one hour!
That?
Horse Grill.
Who is it?
Horse Girl.
He's talking about Jesse!
Well, open it now!
Dog!
Enjoy the shellfish, ghost!
No, no, no!
¡Lily!
Yes, can I help you?
Oh?
One moment.
Fascinating.
¡Lily!
Go back to the Horse Girl post!
That?
He has to do everything you say!
He's getting away, Boss!
¡Lily!
Don't let him go!
Go back to the post!
Yes, yes.
Bonnie needs to see this.
Don't close them.
Where is?
Hey, Lili.
Share it.
Share it now.
We did it.
Where was it seen?
It is.
The printer.
Yeah.
I've finished now.
Bonnie just had breakfast.
No, I'm done.
I have to go play, Mom, I've already started.
What now, albarrador?
Well, you're the construction worker, construction worker.
Where did this photo come from, Bonnie?
Why did you put them in the garage?
Uh, because Bonnie asked me to, remember?
my dad?
No.
He doubted that Lili Padme sent the message.
They're not here.
Jesse was found and he already threw the
white.
I hope you are well.
The queen is in a safe place.
Yes, you can do it, agent.
One of them deactivates the bomb.
But which one is it?
Lone agent.
Healthy, sanitary.
Oh, no.
OK.
Follow me, Your Majesty.
But what?
That was incredible.
I was a spy.
Yes, you were.
You were the best spy.
To split?
That was wonderful.
That, my friend, was playing.
We already played you.
This is what it means to be a toy commissioner.
Yes, it's how I feel, it's the first time
that you call me commissioner without mocking me.
But now I understand.
Lesa is the perfect friend for Bonnie, because playing
She feels the same way about her.
That's how you play, my little girl.
It's her.
Yes, he saw the message.
Answer him!
Do it!
Okay, okay, what do I have to do?
¡Hey!
Oh yes!
Excellent!
He's coming!
Pony is coming here!
Lazy Pony are going to meet!
¡Marty!
What are you writing?
Delete that right now!
Yeah!
I wanted to get some batteries out of all this.
What are they saying?
Kink, talk to me.
I can't hear, there's too much commotion.
Tell him how to get rid of us.
Do you think they're going to donate to us?
Dona.
No, Karencita, they were donated.
I love her, but it's going to be difficult.
Call him!
Did you hear something?
They're just a few steps.
Oh, how sweet.
Careful!
Bonnie is coming in!
Run, Mom!
Oh no, Lili too, dad.
Calm down, Bonnie.
I don't think you...
Listen, Dad, you stay here.
I'm going too.
Because?
Why only you?
Because I have more experience in the field than
You, that's all.
Don't you think I'm capable?
No, I just think I would do it a
a little...
better.
You don't deserve this.
Oh, Dad, don't get angry.
It's because I was put in charge.
That's why you must stay here to take care of the
room.
There's no room without Jesse.
Peace!
¡No!
¡Bonnie!
None!
¡Poncho!
It's good to see them fight again.
It brings back memories.
How did your toys get here?
Oh, have you seen this one?
Oh, this one has puppies.
I'm going to save this one.
Has it arrived yet?
Be careful.
Dad might see you.
Don't believe it.
He'll be showing off those funds forever.
It's her!
It's Bonnie!
She was aiming!
It's really here.
Really.
Bonnie, let's go get them.
Thank you.
Listen.
I just wanted...
Thank you, friends.
They were very useful devices.
That's done.
The drainage system takes them away.
It's her!
Hello.
Can I help them?
I'm sorry to bother you, but we received this message from your
it is.
He found some of my daughter's toys.
Are they there?
I'm going to call her.
¿Blaze?
Is it?
Yeah?
Can you bring the dolls you found?
Its owner is here.
Our Lady?
¿Blaze?
Is she...? She's Bonnie.
Hi, Bonnie.
Hello.
Are the toys yours?
I don't play with boring toys.
The thing is...
son...
antiques.
Yes, they are somewhat old.
I imagine they must be worth something, right?
No, they're not valid.
Keep them.
A.
Bonnie, don't you want them anymore?
Are you sure?
Bonnie.
I don't know what's happening to him.
I apologize for bothering you.
It's no trouble.
Bonnie, if you change your mind, just...
unknown
I don't understand.
What happened?
Why did you do that, Bonnie?
Okay, I think we'll go.
Quick, come with them!
It's too late for me, my friend.
But maybe not for you.
Tell me he didn't hit the target.
¿Commissaria?
Jessie?
Are you OK?
What happened?
Jessie abandoned them.
It's all their fault!
Children now grow faster because of using
so many devices.
They stole our time!
I wanted to make a difference!
I had to make a difference!
And they ruined it!
Are you OK?
Forgive me.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
To make a rag, you hit hard, cowgirl.
¿Commissaria?
Forgive me, Smarty.
It's not you.
I'm the only useless one.
Poor Jessie!
We need to search with...
¡Boss!
Where are you going?
We need to talk about it first!
What's going on?
And your name?
And your purpose?
Calm down, calm down.
Take it away!
Where am I?
Why am I here?
My poncho!
Silence, murderer!
Killer?
No, I'm not...
¿Boss?
How do you know who we are?
Who sent you?
Oh no, not again!
Speaks!
Talk about what?
What am I supposed to know?
She's wearing a holster!
You were positioned outside our fortress
leader.
You are an agent of Zorg.
Concern?
¡No!
I don't even know who their leader is!
You're lying!
Do you want to hurt the red-haired maiden with the
symbol of the star command?
Jessie!
Wait!
He is not an agent of Zorg.
And who is the grandfather?
Why does everyone say that?
I'm not that old!
This grandpa is a toy.
A toy?
Yes, we are all toys.
Our mission on this planet is to make people happy.
to a child.
Play!
What did he say about playing?
Don't play!
¡Boss!
You can ask them to look for us in their feelings!
Everyone knows that's true.
And the one with reddish hair is the leader
of the toys.
Her name is Commissioner Jessie.
Commissioner Jessie!
And the commissioner is trapped inside the
strength.
We have to infiltrate them and rescue her along with her
leal corcel.
Why do you know all this?
Because I am your sheriff.
A stellar commando!
So, is that grandpa a toy?
He who knows the truth!
Ah, yes, him.
He's my assistant.
Tithe.
And by the way, surprise.
Zurg is our father!
¡No!
Yeah!
Honey, what are you thinking?
I don't know.
I hope that girl is okay.
Calm.
Ladies?
Is anyone hungry?
They!
Do you know how to eat pasta today, Dad?
Uh, I like the way you think, my love.
¡Esperense!
Not here!
Not here at all!
Good heavens!
Where could she have gone?
Commander, we infiltrated these devices.
Hey!
¡Microchipen!
Don't touch!
I'm receiving a super touch signal!
I have all my bars!
Don't worry, I can map kilometers.
They have their own access point!
Oh no, they're one of his own.
They're one of us!
How crazy!
Listen, this one doesn't seem to work.
Where are you hiding Jessie, buddy?
Hey, relax!
We are friends of Jessie!
And I have a name.
Smarty Pants.
Hygiene instructor.
Go and clean!
I'm serious, Mr. Gadget.
It is my sworn duty as a space guardian.
My name is sir!
I'm coming!
We're all friends with Jessie here.
Can you tell us where it is?
He went to Swing Hill.
On the other side of the ranch.
We can't walk there.
Well, we need to get transported.
Commander Lightyear!
What do I see?
Bonnie, did something bad happen to your friends?
Teach me.
You didn't do anything wrong, I promise you.
Oh, daughter.
You know you can always talk to me and
with dad.
Whatever.
Because we love you, Bonnie.
Lot.
I wouldn't change a thing about you.
And a true friend would feel the same.
Don't you think so?
We need to take a break from that chat for a while.
¿ok?
Let's get some ice cream.
I can give you this one if you want.
¡Corre!
Thank you so much.
¿Bonnie?
There are no chocolate chips.
Choose another flavor.
¡Bonnie!
Where are you, Bonnie?
Forgive me, Bonnie.
That?
What's happening?
You shouldn't have followed me!
Oh, you spoiled horse.
Go live with Blaze, bullseye.
You'll be better off there.
I'm serious.
I know she'll take good care of you.
And he has other horses.
Yourself!
I can't do it again.
I can't love another child just for
that he ends up forgetting me.
I couldn't stand it anymore.
I never wrote that.
It had to be...
¿Emily?
Wait.
These are not Emily's things.
Son...
newer ones.
This doesn't make sense.
She wouldn't have had these things.
By then...
She was already an adult.
Wait for me.
Emily...
He named his daughter...
My name.
Can you believe it?
Careful!
Jessie?
Target shooting!
¡Ey!
I found them!
¿Emily?
¡Bob!
Jessie!
Are you OK?
What are you doing here?
We came for you, Jessie.
For me?
All of us.
We have many buses.
Like fifty, but I only know about two.
¡Ok, ok!
Calm down!
Let her breathe!
Your?
Yeah?
¡Ey!
He was talking to me.
Only me.
We saw when Bonnie gave you a gift.
Oh really?
I still don't understand it.
You're not useless, commissioner.
We love you!
And a lot!
Hey, I'm fine.
Bonnie is growing up.
And it's not up to us to decide how and when.
It's going to happen.
What matters is that we were there when
It was needed and we helped it grow.
And I like to think that we did it.
And that's why we're so proud, Jessie.
Sorry, it was unintentional.
It's a shame he couldn't connect with Blaze.
Wait!
Connect!
It's not too late!
LilyPud can connect them!
LilyPud?
Come on, it's a new message!
Jessie, forgive me!
They weren't the right friends.
I hurt Bonnie.
Oh, no, Bonnie!
Smartie, send the answer!
You can fix it!
As?
He says, I can't.
I discarded myself.
That?
In the donation truck.
By my cat's whiskers.
Now he decides to do that?
We have to go after her!
That?
But how?
Smartie, tell Lily to send a photo
Where is he from!
List!
Snappy, assume the blurry sign!
Who knows about technology now!
Martin Avenue!
Atlas, can you guide us to the truck?
I've already marked the path, cowgirl!
Tell Lily to send more photos of
where is!
Let's go get her!
Yes, police station!
Jessie, when you have a chance, there's something you should ask me!
To ask you?
I'm sorry if you say something like that.
Can you help me with this?
Yes, police station!
Wait for us!
It's not far!
If we go south, it's five blocks!
And to the east, times two!
Maybe we'll catch up with her before we get on the highway!
Car!
Free!
He passed by a gas station!
Haha, a fart passed!
Joke, it doesn't fall for it!
Almost!
There's an attraction!
Next street on the right!
Free!
It's a house!
It tells me there's a street here!
Maybe there was one five years ago!
Old map!
Recalculating!
There's no time!
Let's cross!
Do you want to cross?
Stay still, puppy!
Free!
The truck!
I see it!
Forward!
Follow me!
Yes, police station!
Free!
We have arrived at our destination!
¡Lily!
Lily, where are you?
¡Hey, Lily!
Yeah?
Can I help you?
¡Lily!
Everything's fine!
We found you!
You shouldn't have come, Jessie.
There's no time for sentimentality, Lily.
Bonnie needs you to be a friend.
Me?
But...
I made a big miscalculation, Jessie.
Heidi, you were right.
Bonnie is different.
He deserves better.
¿Lily?
Didn't you know those girls were bad for
Bonnie?
¡No!
I'm mean to Bonnie!
I'm the one who caused this!
Well, help me fix it!
I found Bonnie, the perfect friend!
Oh really?
Yeah!
We need to connect them, lilipas!
¡Ok!
But first we have to get everyone down from the
truck and return.
Oh!
Come on, Boy!
Let's get off quickly!
And we drift further apart every second!
I know there has to be a solution!
We have these modern buses!
Excuse me, if you'll excuse me!
I'm going through!
Spaceman, turn around!
¡Wow!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Don't go overboard!
Uh, yeah!
He went too far!
Ready, commissioner?
Echale, Lily!
¡Wow!
They will be free!
Arrogant!
Damn it!
And this time they connect!
¡Jesse!
What if Boy B rejects you again?
If they become friends, then it's worth it!
Yes, commissioner!
Wait, Jesse!
Wait!
That?!
What do you want?
Just listen to me!
I was trying to ask you that and...
If I don't do it now, I won't.
to do.
Would you like to...? Just do what you want!
Are you my boyfriend now, Albacín?
Rest, guardian.
Rest.
GOOD?
Are you doing well on your mission?
Yes, Commander!
One, two!
That?
Where is it?
Evil Papacy!
What are you doing here?
She's one of us, accept it.
Pay close attention!
Lili and Jessica have a plan to help
a Bonnie.
Okay, what do you need us to do?
Nothing.
That?
Nothing?
How easy!
Jessica already did the hard work.
Typical Jessica.
The only thing missing is for him to send a
message.
Now it's up to the girls.
Come here, little one, I found it in the car.
Don't worry, just turn off the chat.
Bonnie, they're looking for you at the door.
Hi Bonnie, I brought your dolls.
Bonnie, at least she says hello.
Ok.
Hello.
Sorry, I didn't play with you.
I played with her a little yesterday.
It's funny when she says, "I'm not afraid of..."
nothing cowboy-like.
That was very strange.
Sorry to bother you.
What are you doing?
Don't let him go, don't let him go.
Law!
I like your boots.
And I like your socks.
What does my beard like, madam?
I'm impressed, milady.
Yes, I'm a thousand years old.
You look so long and silky.
Do you want to come and play?
Ok.
And are you a horse?
A real one?
Yes, it's true.
I know, I have a good idea.
Please take good care of my son.
Friends, we have gathered today to bear witness
of the most wonderful union of the commissioner
Jessie y Vostolomeo MacLightyear.
Okay, commissioner, you can put that ring on him.
tiny finger of yours and pronounce your
votes.
Your?
Would you accept this ring as my absolute promise of
to have fun and play together and all that for
the rest of my days?
Even the bad ones?
I accept!
Did you see my wedding ring?
Have you checked the bathroom yet?
We're missing something, what do you think?
¡Flory!
From the garden?
Let's go!
Arrive!
Congratulations to both of you!
Don't worry, I took lots of pictures for Smarty and the
band.
That!
That's very sweet of you, Lily.
Good job, commissioner.
You can call me Jessica.
Okay, I'll do it, Jessica.
Did you know?
No no.
Ok.
Hey, when you have a chance, could you introduce me to the one who
Was she wearing the ring?
What a heartthrob!
Ok.
Here it comes!
It's perfect!
Great idea!
The wedding continues!
¡Ok!
Let's go!
Will you accept me as your super cool wife, commissioner?
I accept!
And will you accept me as your handsome guardian husband?
Space?
I accept!
Then I pronounce them!
Don't oppose me!
Our husband is already married!
With me!
This is the third time this has happened to me!
same!
How could you do that!
Jessie!
This is not what you think!
Tell them Buzz!
Tell them about our love!
But Dixie, that was back then!
And now is now.
Kiss me!
This didn't win.
It's a suit.
Congratulations.
You're a great sheriff.
What if you helped?
Yes, we just followed the guide!
Woody, do you want some?
Hold this, I'll drive.
Oh, dear.
Are...
They're so good.
Good.
In mode...
What if Trixie ruined the wedding cake?
But Trixie, why?
Do you want to stay the night with me?
Yes, I would like that very much.
Now, a selfie.
Friends forever, cowgirl.
Let's go.
-Where are we going?
-To Neptune.
-What are you doing?
-We're going on our honeymoon.
-Do you want to come?
-Yes!
Soy Buzz Lightyear.
To infinity and beyond.
Hey...
Mission accomplished.
We meet again, my son.